I... I think that's what I meant.
أنا... أعتقد أن هذا ما قصدته.
I like Kon-chan.
انا احب كون تشان.
Just kidding! I was messing with you.
أنا أمزح فقط! كنت أمزح معك.
I'll head out first, then.
سأخرج أولاً إذن.
Hey! Hayakawa.
مهلا! هاياكاوا.
Was what you said back then really a lie?
هل كان ما قلته حينها كذبة حقا؟
What happened back then...
ماذا حدث حينها...
If it wasn't a lie, would you seriously consider it?
لو لم تكن كذبة هل ستفكر فيها جديا؟
You go ahead and sleep! I'm going to take a shower.
اذهب ونم! سأستحم.
Hayakawa.
هاياكاوا.
It's really great to see you again.
من الرائع حقًا رؤيتك مرة أخرى.
I originally planned to keep my feelings for Kon-chan sealed away in my heart.
لقد خططت في البداية أن أبقي مشاعري تجاه كون تشان مختومة في قلبي.
Don't look back...
لا تنظر للخلف...
"Depth of Field"
"عمق المجال"
(Episode 6)
(الحلقة 6)
Were you just testing it out earlier?
هل كنت تقوم باختباره للتو في وقت سابق؟
Yeah, that's right.
نعم، هذا صحيح.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
There was a bit of a mistake just now.
لقد كان هناك خطأ بسيط للتو.
- I've been giving it my all in practice. - Alright, alright!
- لقد بذلت قصارى جهدي في التدريب. - حسنًا، حسنًا!
Hayakawa, don't overdo it with the practice.
هاياكاوا، لا تبالغ في التدريب.
Hey! Take a break for a bit.
مهلا! خذ استراحة قليلا.
(Konno: Want to grab something to eat?)
(كونو: هل تريد أن تأكل شيئًا؟)
(Hayakawa: Sure.)
(هايكاوا: بالتأكيد.)
(Konno: My friend wants to meet you.)
(كونو: صديقي يريد مقابلتك.)
Friend...
صديق...
I really am such an idiot.
أنا حقا أحمق.
Still holding on to a bit of hope.
لا أزال متمسكًا بقليل من الأمل.
You haven't changed at all since high school.
لم تتغير على الإطلاق منذ المدرسة الثانوية.
Sorry for asking you out all of a sudden.
آسف لأنني طلبت منك الخروج فجأة.
Not at all...
مُطْلَقاً...
You two are...?
أنتما الإثنان...؟
We were college classmates.
كنا زملاء في الكلية.
Since our student ID numbers were close, we naturally got to know each other.
وبما أن أرقام هويتنا الطلابية كانت قريبة، فقد أصبحنا نعرف بعضنا البعض بشكل طبيعي.
Yeah, that may be true, but Konno is the kind of person who really takes photography seriously.
نعم، قد يكون هذا صحيحًا، لكن كونو هو نوع الشخص الذي يأخذ التصوير الفوتوغرافي على محمل الجد حقًا.
So I just wanted to get to know him.
لذلك أردت فقط التعرف عليه.
- That's the first time I've heard you say that. - And... it feels like he's really well-connected?
- هذه هي المرة الأولى التي أسمعك تقول ذلك. - و... يبدو وكأنه يتمتع بعلاقات جيدة حقًا؟
- I don't have any connections. - Sure you do.
- ليس لدي أي اتصالات. - بالتأكيد لديك.
Introduce your father to me!
عرّفني على والدك!
Introduce you to my dad? Are you planning to fly to New York?
هل أقدمك إلى والدي؟ هل تخطط للسفر إلى نيويورك؟
Hey! Wanna go check it out?
مرحباً! هل تريد أن تذهب لتفقده؟
No way! You should just take me with you!
مستحيل! لازم تاخدني معاك!
Because New York has Broadway and the Statue of Liberty.
لأن نيويورك لديها برودواي وتمثال الحرية.
It's basically one of the hottest spots for photos!
إنه في الأساس أحد أكثر الأماكن سخونة لالتقاط الصور!
- Have you been there? - Yeah, I have.
- هل كنت هناك؟ - نعم، لقد كنت هناك.
I want to go too!
أريد أن أذهب أيضاً!
If you take photos there, I bet you could attract some models, right?
إذا قمت بالتقاط صور هناك، فأنا أراهن أنك قد تتمكن من جذب بعض النماذج، أليس كذلك؟
Ah! Speaking of models. Hayakawa, could you take a look at this for me?
آه! بالحديث عن النماذج. هاياكاوا، هل يمكنك إلقاء نظرة على هذا؟
This is the one.
هذا هو.
This... is this Miss Nan's work?
هذا... هل هذا عمل الآنسة نان؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
That's impressive.
هذا مثير للإعجاب.
That's amazing.
هذا مدهش.
Actually, I really like it.
في الواقع، أنا أحب ذلك حقًا.
Hey! I'm so happy!
مهلا! أنا سعيد جدًا!
Actually, I invited you out today because I wanted you to be my model, Hayakawa.
في الواقع، دعوتك للخروج اليوم لأنني أردتك أن تكون عارضتي، هاياكاوا.
Model?
نموذج؟
Yes! It fits my image perfectly!
نعم! إنه يناسب صورتي تمامًا!
And I keep having the urge to shoot Hayakawa again.
ولا زلت أشعر بالرغبة في إطلاق النار على هاياكاوا مرة أخرى.
You get it, right?
لقد فهمت ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
The urge...
الرغبة...
Sometimes you just have that feeling.
في بعض الأحيان يكون لديك هذا الشعور فقط.
By the way, which one's your favorite?
بالمناسبة، ما هو المفضل لديك؟
- I really like this one. - Right? It's great, isn't it?
- أعجبني هذا حقًا. - صحيح؟ رائع، أليس كذلك؟
How did you shoot this?
كيف قمت بتصوير هذا؟
Looks like it's in a puddle, doesn't it?
يبدو وكأنه في بركة، أليس كذلك؟
This is the one. I used the puddle to take this shot.
هذه هي. استخدمت البركة لالتقاط هذه الصورة.
See, there's a reflection. That way, it's handled really cleanly.
انظر، هناك انعكاس. بهذه الطريقة، يتم التعامل معه بشكل نظيف للغاية.
- Sorry about that. - Yeah, yeah, that's it.
- آسف بشأن ذلك. - نعم، نعم، هذا هو الأمر.
- Coming right up.
- قادمًا في الحال.
- Give me a stronger highball. - Sure.
- أعطني كرة عالية أقوى. - بالتأكيد.
You can take your time thinking about what happened earlier, no rush.
يمكنك أن تأخذ وقتك في التفكير فيما حدث في وقت سابق، ولا داعي للاستعجال.
You can really take it easy. No need to feel any pressure.
يمكنكِ أخذ الأمر ببساطة. لا داعي للشعور بأي ضغط.
I'm counting on you.
أنا أعتمد عليك.
- Which round is this? - The second round.
- أي جولة هذه؟ - الجولة الثانية.
Is Konno always like that when he's drunk?
هل كونو دائمًا هكذا عندما يكون في حالة سكر؟
If he drinks too much, he definitely does!
إذا شرب كثيرًا، فإنه يفعل ذلك بالتأكيد!
He smiles about eighty percent more than usual, and he often forgets things.
يبتسم أكثر من المعتاد بنسبة ثمانين بالمائة، وينسى الأشياء في كثير من الأحيان.
Konno, time to go home.
كونو، حان وقت العودة إلى المنزل.
Your place is right here, so if you miss the last train, it actually works out pretty well!
مكانك هنا، لذا إذا فاتك القطار الأخير، فسيكون الأمر في الواقع جيدًا جدًا!
It's actually a bit of a hassle for me when you come by so often, you know.
إنه في الواقع أمر مزعج بعض الشيء بالنسبة لي عندما تأتي إليّ كثيرًا، كما تعلم.
Here, have a drink.
تفضل، تناول مشروبًا.
Sorry... I drank too much.
عذرا... لقد شربت كثيرا.
Oh no... I'm so sleepy.
أوه لا... أنا نعسان جدًا.
Aren't you going to take a shower?
ألا تنوي الاستحمام؟
Still the same, huh.
لا يزال هو نفسه، أليس كذلك؟
Kon-chan...
كون تشان...
Sorry.
آسف.
- Hey! Konno. - Don't call me that.
- هيه! كونو. - لا تناديني بهذا.
Just hearing that makes me mad.
مجرد سماع ذلك يجعلني غاضبًا.
Huh, with a girl? Konno?
هاه، مع فتاة؟ كونو؟
Well, how should I put this... I just kind of went along with it after getting drunk...
حسنًا، كيف يجب أن أضع هذا الأمر... لقد وافقت عليه بعد أن سُكرت...
Hmm... I've never seen it myself! Haven't even heard about it.
هممم... لم أرَه بنفسي! ولم أسمع عنه حتى.
By the way, what's the relationship between Miss Nan and Konno?
بالمناسبة، ما هي العلاقة بين الآنسة نان وكونو؟
Huh, us? No, no, that's not possible.
هاه، نحن؟ لا، لا، هذا غير ممكن.
I see.
أرى.
Once again... you're thinking "maybe," aren't you?
مرة أخرى... أنت تفكر "ربما"، أليس كذلك؟
Honestly, this probably isn't the best time for him to be in a relationship, right?
بصراحة، ربما هذا ليس الوقت المناسب له للدخول في علاقة، أليس كذلك؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
See, he's about to leave Japan soon, isn't he?
انظر، إنه على وشك مغادرة اليابان قريبًا، أليس كذلك؟
- What? - Huh? You haven't heard yet?
- ماذا؟ - هاه؟ لم تسمع بعد؟
He was planning to take a break from school for a while to help out because his dad is overseas.
كان يخطط لأخذ استراحة من المدرسة لفترة من الوقت للمساعدة لأن والده في الخارج.
Didn't we say yesterday that it was in New York?
ألم نقول بالأمس أنها كانت في نيويورك؟
So I don't think he's planning on dating anyone right now.
لذا لا أعتقد أنه يخطط لمواعدة أي شخص في الوقت الحالي.
I see.
أرى.
Sorry, I thought Konno had already told you.
آسف، اعتقدت أن كونو قد أخبرك بالفعل.
After all, it's been three years since we last saw each other.
بعد كل شيء، لقد مرت ثلاث سنوات منذ أن رأينا بعضنا البعض آخر مرة.
Alright then, talk to you later. Goodbye.
حسناً، سأتحدث إليك لاحقاً. مع السلامة.
So warm.
دافئ جداً.
Absolutely stunning today.
مذهلة تماما اليوم.
- Hold on, hold on. - What's up?
- انتظر، انتظر. - ماذا يحدث؟
- Hey! Isn't that awesome? - It really is!
- هيه! أليس هذا رائعًا؟ - إنه رائع حقًا!
Hayakawa.
هاياكاوا.
- Sorry. - Oh no.
- آسف. - أوه لا.
- What's up? - Look.
- ماذا هناك؟ - انظر.
This Sunday, someone from Nouvelle Records wants to meet and have a chat!
في هذا الأحد، يريد أحد أعضاء شركة Nouvelle Records الالتقاء بنا والدردشة معنا!
I heard they came to see our performance last time.
سمعت أنهم جاءوا لرؤية أدائنا في المرة الأخيرة.
- Uh, that! - That!
- أوه، هذا! - هذا!
- Huh? - That's awesome!
- هاه؟ - هذا رائع!
How about we pick a place and have a strategy meeting?
ماذا عن اختيار مكان وعقد اجتماع استراتيجي؟
Coming, coming, coming!
قادم، قادم، قادم!
- Hayakawa! Hurry up, hurry up! - Coming! Coming!
هاياكاوا! أسرع، أسرع! - قادم! قادم!
(I want to return your key.)
(أريد أن أعيد مفتاحك.)
Sorry about the keys. I heard you're heading to New York.
آسف بشأن المفاتيح. سمعت أنك متجه إلى نيويورك.
You can head home early today.
يمكنك العودة إلى المنزل مبكرًا اليوم.
By the way, is it really necessary to work this late?
بالمناسبة، هل من الضروري حقًا العمل في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
At the very least, let me help clean up a bit before I go.
على الأقل دعني أساعدك في التنظيف قليلًا قبل أن أذهب.
Alright, I'll leave it to you then.
حسنًا، سأترك الأمر لك إذن.
Good job.
أحسنت.
What's up, are you two a couple?
ما الأمر، هل أنتما زوجين؟
No.
لا.
So... is it someone you want to be in a relationship with?
إذن... هل هذا هو الشخص الذي تريد أن تكون في علاقة معه؟
Just friends.
مجرد أصدقاء.
There was a bit of a pause just now.
لقد كان هناك توقف قليلًا الآن.
You don't have to hide it, it's okay.
لا داعي لإخفاء الأمر، لا بأس بذلك.
I've been through that myself before.
لقد مررت بهذا بنفسي من قبل.
Is this... the kind of liking that comes from friendship? Or is it something more...?
هل هذا... الإعجاب الذي ينبع من الصداقة؟ أم هو أكثر من ذلك...؟
I used to think we were just friends.
كنت أعتقد أننا مجرد أصدقاء.
Even though he's a bit clumsy.
على الرغم من أنه أخرق بعض الشيء.
But I like the way he gives it his all.
لكني أحب الطريقة التي يبذل بها كل ما لديه.
I just want to be there by his side, watching him.
أريد فقط أن أكون هناك بجانبه، وأراقبه.
But we were apart for too long...
لكننا كنا منفصلين لفترة طويلة...
What got everyone started with music in the first place?
ما الذي دفع الجميع إلى البدء بالموسيقى في المقام الأول؟
I was influenced by my older brother.
لقد تأثرت بأخي الأكبر.
Hayakawa comes from a family of musicians.
ينتمي هاياكاوا إلى عائلة من الموسيقيين.
I see.
أرى.
So have you been living with music ever since you were a kid?
فهل كنت تعيش مع الموسيقى منذ أن كنت طفلاً؟
I also had a period when I stepped away from music.
لقد مررت أيضًا بفترة ابتعدت فيها عن الموسيقى.
I made up my mind never to touch it again.
لقد قررت أن لا ألمسه مرة أخرى.
So you had a time like that too?
فهل كان لديك وقت مثل هذا أيضًا؟
Why do you want to start over again?
لماذا تريد أن تبدأ من جديد؟
That's...
هذا...
Someone once told me to be honest with my own feelings.
لقد أخبرني أحدهم ذات مرة أن أكون صادقًا مع مشاعري.
He told me, you can make choices for yourself.
قال لي، يمكنك اتخاذ القرارات بنفسك.
Yeah! It's really lucky to meet someone like that.
نعم! من حسن حظي أن ألتقي بشخص مثله.
Yes.
نعم.
Hayakawa, isn't it thanks to that person that you're able to live so honestly now?
هاياكاوا، أليس بفضل هذا الشخص أنك قادر على العيش بصدق الآن؟
Being honest with myself...
أن أكون صادقا مع نفسي...
- Thank you all for coming today. - Thank you for giving us this opportunity.
- شكرا لكم جميعا على حضوركم اليوم. - شكرا لكم على منحنا هذه الفرصة.
Ah! I'm so nervous.
اه! أنا متوترة جدًا.
I feel pretty good.
أنا أشعر أنني بحالة جيدة جدًا.
Right, Hayakawa!
حسنًا، هاياكاوا!
- Hayakawa? - Ah! Sorry.
- هاياكاوا؟ - آه! آسف.
I'm heading out first.
سأخرج أولاً.
- Huh?
- هاه؟
Miss Nan, is Konno with you right now?
آنسة نان، هل كونو معك الآن؟
I have something I want to say to him.
عندي شيء أريد أن أقوله له.
Konno has already left for New York.
لقد غادر كونو بالفعل إلى نيويورك.
Why...
لماذا...
So cold.
بارد جداً.
(Strawberry milk)
(حليب الفراولة)
Why are you already drinking? We haven't even toasted yet!
لماذا تشرب الآن؟ لم نحتفل بعد!
Cheers!
هتافات!
Sorry.
آسف.
I'm going to start eating.
سأبدأ بالأكل.
I heard you're heading to New York.
سمعت أنك متجه إلى نيويورك.
I heard it from Miss Nan.
سمعت ذلك من الآنسة نان.
I... was planning to tell you when I returned the keys.
كنت أخطط أن أخبرك عندما أرجع المفاتيح.
Sorry, I'm the one who didn't reply to your messages.
عذرا، أنا الذي لم أرد على رسائلك.
Actually, weren't you supposed to leave today?
في الواقع، ألم يكن من المفترض أن تغادر اليوم؟
Yeah.
نعم.
But...
لكن...
it's been changed to tomorrow night.
لقد تم تغييره إلى ليلة الغد.
Because I want to talk with you.
لأنني أريد التحدث معك.
I want to talk with you too.
أريد أن أتحدث معك أيضاً.
Thank you for everything back in high school.
شكرا لك على كل شيء في المدرسة الثانوية.
That's why I'm still making music now.
ولهذا السبب مازلت أصنع الموسيقى الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
That's what I should've told you first when we met again.
هذا ما كان يجب أن أخبرك به أولًا عندما التقينا مرة أخرى.
In the end, it still feels like I'm avoiding you.
في النهاية، لا أزال أشعر أنني أتجنبك.
Sorry.
آسف.
Don't apologize.
لا تعتذر.
That was the result of your own hard work.
لقد كانت هذه نتيجة عملك الجاد.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I never expected you to act like that when you're drunk.
لم أتوقع أبدًا أن تتصرف بهذه الطريقة عندما تكون في حالة سكر.
You probably wouldn't remember anyway after drinking that much.
ربما لن تتذكر على أية حال بعد شرب كل هذه الكمية.
I remember.
انا أتذكر.
But Miss Nan said you get amnesia when you're drunk.
لكن الآنسة نان قالت أنك تصاب بفقدان الذاكرة عندما تكون في حالة سُكر.
I remember.
انا أتذكر.
Kon-chan, you...
كون تشان، أنت...
Do you kiss anyone when you're drunk?
هل تقبل أحدا عندما تكون في حالة سكر؟
I don't kiss just anyone.
أنا لا أقبل أي شخص.
I only did it because it was you.
لقد فعلت ذلك فقط لأنه كان أنت.
Alright!
على ما يرام!
Let me confess my feelings again, to make up for what happened three years ago.
دعني أعترف بمشاعري مرة أخرى، للتعويض عما حدث قبل ثلاث سنوات.
Alright!
على ما يرام!
Kon-chan.
كون تشان.
I like Kon-chan in that same way.
أنا أحب كون تشان بنفس الطريقة.
This time... I'm not lying.
هذه المرة... أنا لا أكذب.
Even last time... I wasn't lying, either.
حتى المرة الأخيرة... لم أكن أكذب أيضًا.
Me too...
أنا أيضاً...
I like you in the same way.
أنا أحبك بنفس الطريقة.
I always thought... I had to keep it hidden.
لقد اعتقدت دائمًا... أنه يتعين علي إبقاء الأمر مخفيًا.
No more lying from now on, okay?
لا مزيد من الكذب من الآن فصاعدا، حسنًا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Hot pot, can we pause for a moment?
وعاء ساخن، هل يمكننا التوقف للحظة؟
Huh?
هاه؟
I want three years' worth of kisses.
أريد قبلات ثلاث سنوات.
And for all the kisses we won't get to share in the days ahead, too.
ولكل القبلات التي لن نتمكن من مشاركتها في الأيام القادمة أيضًا.
I really miss this.
أنا أفتقد هذا حقا.
I've heard this song here before, too.
لقد سمعت هذه الأغنية هنا من قبل أيضًا.
Yeah.
نعم.
Uh... this...
أوه... هذا...
This song was inspired by Kon-chan.
هذه الأغنية مستوحاة من كون تشان.
Don't call me gross.
لا تناديني بفظيع.
- Ugh~ That's so gross! So gross! - Are you even listening to me?
- آه، هذا مقرف جدًا! مقرف جدًا! - هل تستمع لي حقًا؟
Hey, want to go grab something to eat?
مرحبًا، هل تريد أن تذهب لتتناول شيئًا ما؟
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
What do you want to eat?
ماذا تريد أن تأكل؟
Meat.
لحمة.
Not bad!
ليس سيئًا!
I want to have ginger pork.
أريد أن آكل لحم الخنزير بالزنجبيل.
Kon-chan, you're treating us, right?
كون تشان، أنت تعالجيننا، أليس كذلك؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
(This story is purely fictional.)
(هذه القصة خيالية بحتة.)